<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Corgineer - misc</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2019-10-23T16:26:00+07:00</updated><entry><title>Hello, world</title><link href="/My-first-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-10-23T16:26:00+07:00</published><updated>2019-10-23T16:26:00+07:00</updated><author><name>Son Vu</name></author><id>tag:None,2019-10-23:/My-first-post.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey, I got it working.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is the &lt;em&gt;first post&lt;/em&gt; from my Pelican blog. &lt;strong&gt;YAY!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of my friends has been urging me to have a blog long time ago, at least since I was in the university. I thought that I was so young and naive back then. By being young and naive, I believed that I was worse than most people all of my personal inquiries might be childish and trivial. True story, just imagine you are an electrical engineering student, and the only kid who was good at computer-related classes, without anyone to compare yourself to. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time flew. I grew up and I had duties: my daily job, my chores, everything. I met people, I read good articles, I got sparks. But I have nowhere to jot it down. I once believed that knowledge is what remained in my head after I forgot everything. You see, how foolish I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until today, it is the time. I decided that I would write a blog. I saw people having their own github.io pages which were cool, because at least I do not have to deal with hosting, databases and all other maintenances. I googled how to created one. The official way is to use Jekyll. But I do not think Jekyll is suitable to my style at least. I tried Ruby a little bit, and it overwhelmed me. I decided not to learn another entire workflow (or force my mind to think as a Ruby programmer) just for a purpose of churning out a blog. A little bit of googling lead me to Pelican. Look's pretty much OK with plugins for almost everything that I might ever need: themes, code highlighting, math formulas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I already had ideas in my mind about what to write about for about some weeks ahead. Computer-related stuffs, maths, physics, biology, photography, gadgets, hacks, etc. Let's see how far I can go with this one...&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>